Hi, I'm Shachi.
We have a guest on the Orca channel today.
Good morning.
Please introduce yourself.
I'm Le Nitrina.
Woooo!
Yes, I'm Mai and this is Haruna Mai.
Mai!
And this is Guro-san and Yuki Ohguro.
Guro!
So, what have you been doing until just now?
Well, we came to eat goldfish.
It's for me!
They came for me! It's true, but...
Lunch.
I think it's this one.
Make a night of it. Flowers.
I can't eat yakiniku ribs.
It was delicious. I had a kumquat bento.
There were about four kinds. I got lost.
Shining Star, if I spell it out, I'll sleep in the rain.
We are called Rumaiguro.
We're a very popular group.
They came to Japan today!
Shining Star, Sleeping in the Rain
Today is the first day we are not in Japan, but we are going to be on TV.
My first time on Japanese TV.
We really appreciate our fans in Japan.
I was invited to sing in a very big and nice TV show called "Pork Village".
Until about 10 minutes ago. Until a few minutes ago. Until just now.Until about 10 minutes ago. Until a while ago. Until a while ago.
Until about 15 minutes ago.
That's right. That's right. Not yet.
The time difference. The time difference.
Time difference. The time difference.
My first TV debut in Japan is over!
Thank you very much.
It was a lot of fun.
We had a live sound... a band.
It was amazing, super gorgeous, and super fun!
And we got to see you all together.
That's right. I was so excited.
It was fun. I caught a glimpse of you during the show.
I thought, "Ha-ha!" I had to look away.
I was looking away.
We all have one thing in common... we're idol nerds.
All three of us.
And so this three-piece unit of nerds, who perform while being watched by their idol idols, are a huge success.
We're going to perform for the nerds who are very successful while being watched by their idol idols.
Three months ago, Yuzuki and I were invited to perform at the Hair Fest, and we talked a lot about what to sing since we all like idols.
Yuzuki's Hair Fest video is up now, so you can see what goes on behind the scenes, but there's more.
I'm also going to perform on stage in Japan.
All three of us!
Oh! Tomorrow.
How's it going?
Tomorrow.
How many times do I have to tell you?
I didn't do it. It's not true.
Here's a couple.
Men.Male
Female
is a way of dividing them.
Male Female
Male
I'm just passing through.
Like Takarazuka-san.
Yes.
I want some bells roses.
I'd like some Versailles roses.
If there were hosts in that era...
I said, "What would it be like?
I'm number one.
That's right.
That's amazing.
It's true.
He used to be a number two host.
They're all over each other.
They're fighting over who gets the number two spot.
One minute she's Gijo, the next she's just a poor girl.
And then there's the poor guy.
And then there's a poor guy who plays a severe.
Or a hostess.
Sounds really difficult.
I've been to a host's party.
While the hosts were dancing in front of me
while the hostesses are dancing in front.
when the hosts are dancing in front of you.There are times when you get excited, aren't there?
When I go to live shows
I know Momokuro, for example, and I do the choreography.
But that image becomes automatic.
It's automatic.
And my teacher told me to do it automatically.
I was told.
That's amazing.
Oh, my God.
It's so real.
How does that feel?
I'm going to change the subject.
When I go to see a live performance of my idol's idols...
I'm the type of person who goes along with the music
Or are you the type of person who tries to follow the idol's movements in various countries?
or are you the type that follows the idol's face with your eyes no matter where you are?
That's a pretty big difference, isn't it?
Even when you're on stage...
There are different types of fans, right?
Like they're right in front of you.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm the type of person who looks at my guesses who are far away from me
than the other members in front of me.
No offense at all.
I'm the type that depends on the song.
Like, it's okay because I'm coming to the center here in the formation of this song.
And I'll look at that girl properly for the "killer part" type.
I see.
I see. I look at the girl next to me.
I see.I see.
I'm sorry if there's a girl in front of me that I don't like, so I look at her, but I'm really scared.
It's a ghost that I'm very careful about.
The moment I knock it down.
He's very considerate.
He's kind.
I glance at it for a moment.
Checking your guess.
It's true that it's a shame to look at the wrong person when they're right in front of you, isn't it?
That's right. I want to look.
I totally understand.
I wondered if they would go this way.
Each to his own.
My eyesight here and my eyesight there are different.
I wish we had a lot of C.K.'s.
Well, yes, I really do.
I don't have enough eyes.
Hey, no thanks.
You're doing this.
I mean, going to live shows.
Really, I guess.
Everyone is,
I mean, you know, the things they've practiced over time,
What they've practiced for a long time,
In a moment,
You have to stop.
Yes, yes.
But maybe, you know, they are,
They're like, "This girl is like this, this girl is like that,
This girl is like this, this girl is like this, this girl is like this,He's like, "This girl is like this,
I'm really detailed.
But, you know, without knowing that
But without knowing it, you can only take a quick look at it, right?
It's hard.
You can't pick up all the details.
That's why I'm thankful for Blu-ray. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
To the management, to the various people, to the people above my guess, thank you.
Thank you for giving me.
I will live.
I hope you will all press the "Rumiglo" button.
If you enjoyed this video, please click the Good button, subscribe to our channel, and comment.
We are on social networking sites, so please follow us on all media and social networking sites.
Thank you very much.
This is Mai Harumizu, in charge of Mai, and Yuji Daikoku, in charge of Guro.
Bye bye.
Please subscribe to our channel.